mobiletoones.com 2019-12-14

# Privacy Policy | Mobile Toones

> [Home](https://www.mobiletoones.com/) > Privacy Policy 

MobileToones.com values the users of our website. Your privacy and trust are very important to us. We recognize that you may be concerned about our collection, use, and disclosure of the personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that we collect when you use the Website and the services offered on the Website ("MobileToones.com Services").   
To understand how we treat the information you give us as you use Mobile Toones, you should read this policy. 

## Personal Information

  * **Non-Account Activity.** You can browse mobile contents, user profiles and watch videos on Mobile Toones without having a Mobile Toones Account. You can also contact us about a particular mobile item without having a Mobile Toones Account. 
  * **Account-Related Activity.** Certain other activities on Mobile Toones—like uploading mobile stuff, posting comments or creating profiles require you to have a Mobile Toones Account. We ask for some personal information when you create a Mobile Toones Account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. 
  * **Usage Information.** We may record information about your usage, such as when you use Mobile Toones, the contacts you communicate with and the frequency and size of data transfers, as well as information you display or click on in Mobile Toones. If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your account. We may use clear GIFs (a.k.a. "Web Beacons") in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. 
  * **Content Uploaded to Site.** Any personal information or mobile content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your playback or profile pages, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. 

## Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

Mobile Toones allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Mobile Toones Sites. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Mobile Toones Site. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. 

Mobile Toones does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. The advertiser may use information regarding your use of the Mobile Toones Site, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks (see links below) for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Mobile Toones's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

Currently, Mobile Toones has relationships with the following third-party ad servers or ad networks: 

  * Google, Inc.   
https://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html 
    * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
    * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
    * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)
  * We partner with ValueClick Media to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick Media may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this "behavioral advertising" practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit [ValueClick Media Website](https://admin.valueclickmedia.com/optout/index.html)
